The video segment shows a vintage black and white portrait of an individual.
The video presents the cover of a significant book, transitioning from the introduction involving a black and white photograph of a person.
A man is gratefully receiving a piece of paper.
The segment presents a Korean news segment with a beetle being shown.
A man is writing on a piece of paper while music plays in the background.
The segment shows a frog.
The scene features a frog.
The segment shows a frog, possibly indicating a focus on natural forms of communication.
The focus of the segment shifts to a frog, possibly indicating a change in topic or perspective.
A man is seen writing on a piece of paper.
A man is composing a letter using a typewriter.
In this segment, a man is seen dressed in a costume, holding a book, and possibly reading from it.
A man dressed in a black robe is seated at a table with a candle, seemingly engaged in some form of contemplation or quiet study.
A man dressed in a historical costume is reading a document, likely presenting historical facts about Vienna in the 17th century.
A letter from the government is being delivered to a household.
The segment discusses Bert von Fischer, a pioneer of European postal services from Bern, who established his own postal company in 1675, which soon expanded throughout the Swiss Confederation.
A courier is seen delivering letters and news from city to city on horseback.
In this segment, the establishment of the Swiss Confederation in 1848 is discussed, highlighting how the monopoly of posts was transferred to the federation, alongside an image of a German soldier's badge.
A man is seen playing a trumpet in the forest.
In the segment, a man, clad in a coat and hat, is standing in the woods with a pipe in his mouth.
The segment shows a serene, snowy forest in winter.
A horse-drawn carriage is journeying down a snowy road in the woods.
A horse is pulling a sleigh through a wooded area.
The horse-drawn postal carriages are now transporting letters and packages at a uniform rate through the forest.
A steam locomotive is seen traveling on a railroad track.
The segment transitions from horse-drawn transport to the introduction of a steam locomotive.
The segment depicts a train journey, possibly part of a news segment on transportation technologies.
In the segment, a train is journeying through a mountain range.
A UFO is being featured in the current segment of the video.
A man in a white coat and hat is standing in the train's doorway.
A man in a white coat is standing in front of a bright yellow light.
A man in a white coat is pouring molten metal into a crucible.
A man dressed in a white coat is standing before a large yellow light bulb.
A man in a white coat is operating a large machine that emits a yellow light.
A scientist in a lab coat is handling a yellow object in a laboratory setting.
The mail is possibly now being transported via rail, with a steam locomotive traveling on a railroad track.
A train is seen traveling on a railway track.
In this segment, a train is seen speeding down the tracks.
A man in a black suit is delivering a news report on a dark stage.
A man is standing alone in a dark room, possibly contemplating about the evolution of railway transportation.
A man in a blue uniform is holding a yellow object.
A man in a blue uniform is handling a package in a kitchen, reflecting the vast number of yearly mail and parcel deliveries made by train.
The segment showcases the utilization of advanced technical tools, such as a conveyor belt system ensuring efficient packaging and distribution of goods.
In segment 44, a film-making machine is being presented or used.
The segment captures a moment as someone concludes their part with a thank you, then shifts to highlight a machine used for making film strips.
The segment is showcasing a sturdy metal box, possibly a noteworthy piece of technology or equipment used in historical communication systems.
The segment shows a film strip being produced by a machine.
The segment presents a news update from MBC about a nuclear reactor.
The segment showcases the operation of a machine that is used to manufacture bottles.
In this segment, the video presents a machine used for film production, enriching the historical overview of communication technologies.
The segment shows a metallic object, possibly a component of a machine related to the film or manufacturing industry.
The segment showcases a box containing film, possibly indicative of the evolution from physical to digital media.
The segment shows the use of a machine for producing film strips.
In this segment, the process of film creation using a machine is being elaborated.
In the segment, a typewriter is being used to imprint invisible ink on a letter.
The sorting machine is automatically directing the letter.
The segment displays a stack of paper documents, possibly indicating the accumulation of information.
The segment showcases a woman playing with a stack of paper documents.
The video segment shows a stack of metal containers in Paris, likely associated with the postal service.
A person is smoothly operating a computer system.
A person is preparing a package for shipment by inspecting a circuit board.
In the segment, someone is making a call using a computer keyboard.
The segment showcases a computer setup including a screen, keyboard, and mouse.
The central control system is being monitored to ensure seamless operation.
A man in a blue shirt is utilizing advanced machinery to significantly automate and expedite a previously laborious process.
The segment shows a measurement being taken from a box of cereal.
A man named Herr Steider is in a control room, working on a computer located in Sector 1.
A woman is sorting mail for destinations outside Europe at an airport post office.
The video segment shows two mannequins, each wearing a dress.
A person is preparing a sewing machine for shipment via airplane.
In this segment, a man is seen holding a sewing machine.
In this segment, an individual is seen holding a sewing machine, wearing a purple shirt, potentially demonstrating a sewing process or fashion design technique.
A person in a purple shirt is featured, possibly continuing the narrative or commentary on the subject.
A tailor has completed sewing a vibrant purple dress.
The segment displays the commonplace nature of airplanes as a modern mode of transportation for mail, illustrated by a baggage carousel at the airport.
The segment shows a jetliner soaring over the cityscape of Chicago.
A man dressed in vintage attire is standing in the woods, expressing his thoughts about the concept of time and God.
In segment 78, there is music being played in the backdrop while the visuals focus on the film and audiovisual equipment belonging to a German company.
A person stands alone in the darkness, creating a sense of anticipation.
The segment features a nostalgic black and white photograph of a person.
The segment introduces the German concept of 'doom' within the context of the documentary.
A man in a gas mask is discussing the early attempts of humans to send signals over long distances, using methods like smoke signals.
In this segment, a Native American man is gratefully acknowledging something before he begins using a blowtorch to burn a buffalo carcass.
In this segment, a Native American woman is seen carrying a large animal over her shoulder while the narration details some historical methods of communication up until the 19th century.
The segment is discussing the network of observatories in Switzerland that existed until the last century, displayed over an image of a city's fortifications map.
The segment explains how in ancient times, structures known as Rutsen were used in sight of each other to transmit emergency signals during war, with an image of a church being shown.
The segment is about American artist Samuel Morse ushering in new communication technology in 1837, accompanied by an image of Abraham Lincoln.
The documentary discusses the rapid development of news transmission technology, showcasing a machine for making paper.
Fifteen years later, the Federal Post could operate a machine that's used for film production.
The Swiss telegraph network is being set into operation with an initial 27 offices, set against the backdrop of the Swiss Alps.
A person is demonstrating how to use a telephone during its early stages of development.
The segment discusses the transmission of messages over long distances, exemplified by a visual of a telephone pole with wires.
The segment shifts to focus on a clockwork mechanism, hinting at the early mechanical innovations in communication technology.
Following the swift transmission of messages over large distances, the segment describes the replacement of Morse code by usual letters using a type printing telegraph on a mechanical keyboard.
The segment shows that the mechanical keyboard, once a cutting-edge invention, has now become a museum artifact.
The segment showcases a telegram being operated using an old-fashioned telephone.
A woman is relaxing on a bed in a room equipped with a computer and a telephone.
A woman is typing on a computer.
A woman is resting on her bed, presumably contemplating about sending a telegram.
A telegraph operator is inside a telephone booth, assumedly carrying out her duties.
In the segment, a person is accepting details for a telegram and typing them into a computer at the University of Toronto's computer lab.
In the segment, a woman is seen working at a computer in a computer room, possibly sending a message or telegram electronically to Zurich.
The message is being transferred to its intended post office, where it will be printed out on a telegram form using a typewriter.
The segment shows a Volkswagen Golf, symbolizing the delivery of a telegram by a courier after modern technological processes.
The segment features a news report being presented by Kim Seong-hyeon and a car with a roof rack is shown.
The segment shows an image of a green emergency medical technician (EMT) sign.
A woman is engaged in business correspondence, typing a message on her typewriter.
In this segment, the documentary is discussing how The Beatles revolutionized communication, similar to the drastic change that the telegram brought about.
A young man is using a typewriter to prepare a text for efficient and cost-effective transmission of messages.
In the segment, a correction is being made on a typewriter.
The segment shows a typewriter and discusses the process of preparing and transmitting text electronically before it is sent over a communication line.
The segment discusses the impact of modern microprocessor technology on data transmission, showing a computer system as part of the explanation.
The segment is discussing the unimaginable future possibilities of computer network technology.
A man in a suit and tie is discussing upcoming services like Videotex that will be offered by PTT, while standing in front of a television set.
The segment shows a man using his television remote control to pull information from a database through his telephone line, indicating the need for additional input from a keyboard.
The segment showcases the first computer in the world to have a graphical user interface, emphasizing on its keyboard.
A man is demonstrating the ease of current technology, sitting comfortably with a computer and a television set.
The segment showcases the film and audiovisual production for the movie "Zinden Film AG".
The segment showcases the film and audiovisual production of a film by 'Zinden Film AG'.
A person is seen standing alone in the dark, hinting at some form of suspense or impending climax.
The documentary concludes a section, possibly showing a telephone as a symbolic representation of the endpoint of the evolution of technology.
The segment features a satellite dish, highlighting the era of advanced communication technologies.
The segment showcases the castle of Dromore town in Northern Ireland.
The segment concludes with the view of a castle.
A man is observed standing on top of a castle tower.
A man is seen surveying the landscape from the top of a castle wall.
The segment showcases a statue of a knight standing majestically atop a tower.
Mark is standing close to the statue of a Roman soldier.
A man dressed in a Roman costume commands from his post atop a wall.
In this segment, the focus is on a statue of a Roman soldier positioned atop a stone wall.
The camera is now fixating on a statue of a man defensively holding a spear and shield.
The video shows a statue of a man in armor, possibly a historic figure or soldier, standing on a stone wall.
The video segment shows a statue of a Roman soldier, possibly discussing a historical narrative about Roman military positions or roles.
The segment showcases a statue of a Roman soldier.
A man is discussing the statue of a warrior holding a spear.
In this segment, a man is seen portraying a Roman soldier, possibly as a part of a historical reenactment.
The segment showcases a statue of a Roman soldier standing on a stone wall, possibly signifying a point in time we reminisce about.
The video segment focuses on a statue of a Roman soldier standing on a stone wall.
The segment presents a narration about the progression of communication in history, symbolized by the recurring depiction of a statue of a Roman soldier.
The focus continues on the statue of a Roman soldier, symbolizing ancient modes of communication.
The segment shows a statue of a man, possibly a soldier, with a sword and shield, signifying an insurmountable boundary.
A man dressed in a black suit is making a presentation against a black backdrop.
In this segment, the narrative is about Alexander Graham Bell in 1876, depicted by an image of a bearded man.
The segment presents a historical reenactment in a courtroom related to John Wilkes Booth, while discussing Alexander Graham Bell's achievement in building a practical telephone.
The segment explains the basic principle of a telephone, demonstrated through a pair of black and white metal horns.
The process of sound wave vibrations being converted by an induction coil, which is symbolized by a spinning wheel, is being explained.
The segment discusses how sound waves propagate through telephone lines, using the analogy of fluctuations in currents, alongside featuring a large metallic object with central cavity, likely a depiction of said sound transmission mechanisms.
In 1877, the Swiss Telegraph Directorate placed an order with a company to advance their communication technology, while a small metallic device is on display.
In this segment, the first telephone experiment conducted by Siemens Halske in Berlin is being discussed, featuring an old small wooden compass.
The segment introduces MBC News correspondent Kim Seong-hyeon reporting from the city of Bern, Switzerland.
The segment shows the starting point between the main station in Bern, Switzerland and the Federal Palace.
In this segment, a woman is describing the history of the telephone service in Switzerland, starting from its initiation in Zurich in 1880.
In this segment, the narration indicates that every larger city had its own telephone system.
The segment showcases the gradual expansion of telephone services to small towns, with systems functioning until the 1950s, depicting a woman using a telephone in a booth.
The segment traces the history of telecommunications in Switzerland, highlighting the technological achievement in 1959 when it became the first country in the world to have a fully automated telephone network.
The increase in the number of subscribers was one of the reasons for the growth of telecommunication network, depicted by many birds perched on a telephone pole.
The segment exhibits a single telephone pole with a line running through it, symbolizing the beginnings of extending the telephone network to remote locations.
The video segment shows a discussion about the relocation of telephone lines in the serene, snow-covered setting of the alpine mountains during sunrise.
A man is in a dark tunnel filled with pipes discussing the advantages of laying cables underground, stressing that they are more protected, secure, and efficient.
In this segment, a man dressed in a blue suit and tie is presenting news from a station platform, with a train visible in the background.
The segment presents a type of coaxial cable capable of transmitting up to 50,000 simultaneous phone calls.
The segment is discussing the development of coaxial cable connections while showing views of the inside of a nuclear reactor.
The segment discusses the development of directional radio technology in Switzerland, set against the visual of a satellite dish.
The segment is explaining the relief and addition of cable connections using a radio tower situated in a mountain range.
In this segment, the commentary reveals that up to 2700 conversations can simultaneously be carried by the broadcast technology, as shown by the image of a television antenna.
The video segment shows a radio tower in a forested area, discussing the modulation of a radio link.
The video segment discusses how intercontinental communications, partially operated via direct beams, are facilitated through satellites, featuring the ground station Leuk in Wallis, which communicates using a large dish antenna.
The segment shows a satellite, named Intel Saat 5, which is part of a larger geostationary telecommunications network.
The segment showcases a large array of radio telescopes, illustrating the connection to other ground stations.
The segment illustrates the usage of a large radio telescope located in the USA for international communication.
The segment shows a transition to discussing the technological progress in communication, focusing on telephony.
A woman in a fancy fur coat and gloves is making a call using a phone in her car.
A man, dressed in a fur coat, is using a mobile phone.
The segment shows a person dressed in a fur coat.
A woman is comfortably seated in a car, engaged in a conversation on her mobile phone.
The segment shows a car driving on a highway.
A car is making its journey along the highway.
In segment 178, a car continues its journey on the highway.
The woman continues her phone conversation while driving her car.
A man dressed in a fur coat and hat is sitting in the woods, holding a briefcase.
The segment shows a bear appearing in the scene.
A lone figure is standing ominously in the dark.
The segment displays the logo for the film 'The Third Man'.
The segment showcases an image of the Berlin Wall.
In this segment, an individual is depicted standing alone in darkness, possibly symbolizing isolation before the advent of lighting or communication technologies.